lowesfoods.com 2012-12-30

# Privacy Policy - Lowe's Food Stores, Inc.

###### Privacy Commitment

Lowe’s Food Stores, Inc. (LFS) places the highest value on the information you share with us and we are committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Policy, which reaffirms LFS’ commitment to maintaining your privacy, discloses the privacy practices governing this site, including how LFS collects, protects and uses your information. For the purpose of this Privacy Policy, "User Information" means any information gathered by LFS about an identified individual, including, but not limited to, name, E-mail address, and telephone number. User Information does not include information that is publicly available.

###### Scope of Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to all users of this site. By accessing this site, you consent to this Privacy Policy and to the collection and use of information by LFS as specified herein. This Privacy Policy is the entire privacy policy for this site and supersedes any prior or contemporaneous communication concerning this subject matter.

###### Collection of User Information

The primary reason that LFS collects and maintains User Information is to identify and verify proper user access to the data and functions within this site. LFS collects information about users during registration to this site and during their participation in certain activities on this site. When a user accesses this site, LFS’ web servers and applications automatically record and track the data made available via the Internet concerning the user. This generic information does not reveal the user's identity and is used in a non-personally identifiable form to improve the site.

###### Use of User Information

The information provided by the user is used for the purpose for which it was provided to identify and verify proper user access to the data and functions within this site and to make contact - via telephone or E-mail - with the user as necessary based upon the functions used and selections made.

LFS does not disclose or sell User Information to any non-affiliated third party. Notwithstanding this policy, LFS retains the right to disclose collected user information if required to do so by law or if acting on a good faith belief that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights or property of LFS, or to respond to an emergency situation.

###### Retention of User Information

Subject to limits imposed by applicable law, LFS retains User Information as long as it believes in its sole discretion such information will be useful or needed. LFS reserves the right to remove User Information from LFS’ records as appropriate.

###### Security

LFS restricts access to nonpublic personal information about you to those of our employees who need to know that information in order to provide proper services to you. LFS employees are bound by LFS’ Code of Ethics and LFS’ other policies concerning access to your data and information. LFS also maintains physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards designed to protect your nonpublic information.

LFS also uses various Virus Protection, Firewalls and Activity Logs as additional security mechanisms.

LFS is not responsible for the content or the privacy policy of third-party sites that contain links from this site.

While LFS and its affiliates have taken various security measures to protect the privacy of the information you submit, we cannot guarantee that computer hackers, security failures, or other attacks will not compromise the confidentiality of your information. We will continue to maintain our dedication to protecting your privacy and data.

###### Transferability of Information

In the event we go through a business transition such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of our assets, your personally identifiable information may be among the assets transferred. You will be notified by means of a notice on this site for at least thirty (30) days of any such change in the ownership or control of your personal information.

###### Compliance with Laws

LFS will comply with applicable federal and state laws regarding its collection and use of your personal information and will limit any disclosures accordingly.

###### Privacy Policy Changes

LFS reserves the right to change this Privacy Policy at any time. Please check back from time to time so you are aware of any changes or updates. The effective date of this policy will be indicated at the top of the page. By continuing to use this site after the posting of any such changes, you accept and agree to the Privacy Policy, as modified.
